<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MagicPaths</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="quit">Info</string>
    <string name="info">info</string>
    
     <string name="formatted_witch_fire">
        <b>Witch Fire</b> \n
        Caster\'s unit suffers a number of hits \n
        equal to the Miscast Roll. The number \n
        of hits cannot exceed the total number \n
        of Wounds in the unit. These hits have \n
        Strength MDU, Magical Attacks and \n
        Armour Piercing (1).
    </string>

    <string name="formatted_amnesia">
        <b>Amnesia</b> \n
        Roll a D6: On 4+, the Wizard cannot\n
        cast the Miscast Spell this game\n
        anymore.
    </string>

    <string name="formatted_catastrophic_detonation">
        <b>Catastrophic Detonation</b> \n
        Roll a D6: On 4+, the Wizard loses \n
        a number of Wounds equal to half \n
        its starting number of Wounds, \n
        rounding fractions up (no saves \n
        of any kind allowed). Miscast Spell \n
        this game anymore.
    </string>

    <string name="formatted_breachVeil">
        <b>Breach in the Veil</b> \n
        Roll a D6: On 4+, the Wizard is \n
        dead, remove it from the game as a \n
        casualty (no saves of any kind \n
        allowed).
    </string>

     <string name="cosmology_duality">
        <b>Duality:</b> All Cosmology spells are divided into two versions; <b>Cosmos</b> and <b>Chaos</b>. When Casting Cosmology spells, always
declare which version of the spell you are using.
Whenever a spell from Cosmology is successfully cast and caster had no Cosmology counter, it gains a counter matching
that version; a <b>Cosmos</b> counter for <b>Cosmos</b> version, or a <b>Chaos</b> counter for <b>Chaos</b> version.
Non-Bound Spells from Cosmology have <font color="#802000">{their Casting Values reduced by 2}</font> when cast by a Caster with a Cosmology
counter matching the version of the Spell that is cast (i.e. Cosmos versions of spells have reduced casting values for
casters with a <b>Cosmos</b> counter, and vice versa for <b>Chaos</b>). When a Caster attempts to cast a Cosmology spell of a version
not matching its counter, it immediately loses its Cosmology counters.
At the end of each of your Magic Phases, replace all your <b>Cosmos</b> counters with <b>Chaos</b> counters, and all <b>Chaos</b> counters
with <b>Cosmos</b> counters.
    </string>

    <string name="the_conclave">
        <b>The Conclave:</b> Spells from Divination gain +3" Range for each other Wizard with non-Bound Spells from Divination,
within 12" of the Caster. Whenever a Wizard attempting to cast a spell from Divination suffers from Lost Focus, all other
friendly Wizards with non-Bound Spells from Divination and within 12" of the Caster also suffer from Lost Focus, until the end of the Magic Phase.
    </string>

    <string name="the_sacrifice">
        <b>The Sacrifice:</b> When casting a non-Bound Spell from this Path, after rolling Magic Dice but before the opponent rolls
any Dispel Attempt, the Active Player may choose to inflict X hits on the Caster\'s unit or another friendly unengaged unit
within 24\". Each unit may only be targeted by this ability once per Magic Phase.
    X is equal to the number of Ranks in the targeted unit, down to a minimum of 2 and up to a maximum of 5. These hits
    wound automatically and no save of any kind is allowed against them. The last model in a unit can never be removed as
    a casualty using this ability (any wound that would reduce its Wound Pool to 0 is discarded).
    If at least one wound was caused, the spell is cast with the <font color="#802000">amplified</font> version. In that case, use any text marked with <font color="brown">{ }</font>
    and ignore any <font color="red">red</font> text.
    </string>

</resources>
